<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" 
      xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
      xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" 
      xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" 
      version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Blog</title>
<link>https://www.jlarps.github.io/index.html</link>
<atom:link href="https://www.jlarps.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<description>A fantastic blog</description>
<generator>quarto-1.2.313</generator>
<lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 07:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<item>
  <title>Post With Code</title>
  <dc:creator>Jared Arp</dc:creator>
  <link>https://www.jlarps.github.io/posts/post-with-code/index.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 




<p>This is a post with executable code.</p>



 ]]></description>
  <category>news</category>
  <category>code</category>
  <category>analysis</category>
  <guid>https://www.jlarps.github.io/posts/post-with-code/index.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.jlarps.github.io/posts/post-with-code/image.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Welcome To My Blog</title>
  <dc:creator>Jared Arp</dc:creator>
  <link>https://www.jlarps.github.io/posts/welcome/index.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 




<p>The project that I have decided to work on is analytics for the Madison High School football team. My job is to create a Logistic Regression to predict what contributes most to the team gaining 4 yards on each down. I will do this by collecting and analyzing unstructured video data of each football game and record that data into an excel sheet. The final presentation will be formatted in R-shiny. I will learn how to use R-shiny and further develop my skills in Logistic Regression. I will also develop my presentation skills so that I can present in a professional manner to the Madison High School’s football coach.</p>
<p><img src="https://www.jlarps.github.io/posts/welcome/thumbnail.jpg" class="img-fluid"></p>
<p>Second Blog Post:</p>
<p>The new project that I have decided to work on is performing a Sentiment Analysis on restaraunt data. I have built the VADER algorithm which takes into account the weight of each word in a sentence and determines the positive, negative, and neutral percentage of the sentence or group of sentences. I have built a python script of the algorithm into Power BI and have created a dashboard for multiple restaraunts that I have web-scraped. The owner(s) can search for a specific word or sentence and find any review that matches. They also can see the positivity, negativity, and neutrality ratio of each Google review.</p>
<p>Third Blog Post:</p>
<p>I have built a scheduled unattended bot using Power Automate to navigate through the Google Reviews API to collect new restaurant data reviews and upload it into a csv file and store it into the data folder. This will allow my client to refresh the data set in Power BI automatically from the online end.</p>



 ]]></description>
  <category>news</category>
  <guid>https://www.jlarps.github.io/posts/welcome/index.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.jlarps.github.io/posts/welcome/thumbnail.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
